



anggaawijaya90@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/anggaawijaya/



github.com/mittenpuss/



dribbble.com/mittenpuss/



mittenpuss.github.io/porto/

# PROFILE

Highly motivated IT magister student, with a strong background in computer science. Experienced in web development and agile development methodologies. Skilled in developing and implementing technical solutions to complex problems, focusing on user experience and performance.

#### SKILLS

Good understanding and skills in Javascript, HTML and CSS

Good understanding and skills for creating a mockup and prototype using **Figma** 

Good understanding and skills for **Front End** Web Development using React JS

Basic understanding and skills for **Back End** Web Development using Node JS and Express JS

Experience in **Designing and Programming** Database using MySQL and Oracle

Good understanding of **Agile Development** Methodologies

Limited experience in using the Google Cloud Platform and Amazon Web Services to host the database

## LANGUAGES

Indonesian

**Native** 

English

Intermediate

TOEFL ITP: 587

# DEWA GEDE ANGGA WIJAYA

# FORMAL EDUCATION

## UNIVERSITY OF INDONESIA (Aug 2021 - present) Temp. GPA: 3.5

Master Degree in Information Technology. Faculty of Computer Science

Activities: Became a teaching assistant for Computer Information Systems courses and coordinated with lecturers to assist 36 students with their assignments and provide feedback

**Thesis**: Evaluation and Interface Design Improvement Recommendations for Toyota Trust E-Commerce Website: A Study Case of PT Astra Auto Trust

# UDAYANA UNIVERSITY (graduated in 2020) GPA: 3.27

Bachelor in Computer Science. Faculty of Mathematics and Natural Sciences.

**Activities**: Active as a member of Student Council on Faculty of Mathematics and Natural Sciences

Final Project: Android-based Balinese Language Learning Application Using Knuth-Morris-Pratt Algorithm

# NON FORMAL EDUCATION

#### DIGITAL TALENT SCHOLARSHIP, FRESH GRADUATE ACADEMY

Database Design and Programming with SQL (Sept - Nov 2020)

The Ministry of Communication and Information Technology selected me for the scholarship. I learned how to design and program a well-structured database. The program is completely done online because of the pandemic. Learning resources were taught using Oracle Academy and creating the Database using Oracle Data Modeler. We used Oracle Application Express (APEX) for the Software Development Environment.

#### SANBERCODE ONLINE BOOTCAMP (July-Oct 2020)

React JS Development and Intermediate React Native Mobile Development

Learned various skill in React JS and React Native Mobile Development.

Fundamental: Gitlab Front End: React Hooks

**Mobile:** Finger Print Authentification, Mapbox, Realtime Data Management, and Deep Linking

### PURWADHIKA CODING AND STARTUP SCHOOL (Jan - July 2020)

Web and Mobile Development Programme

Became the best graduate from the current batch, which consist of 21 people. I also learned various skills in Web and Mobile Development.

Fundamental: Data Structure, Algorithm, Javascript, HTML, CSS, Git, Github.

Front End: React JS, Redux.

Back-End: NodeJS, ExpressJS, MySQL, MongoDB, RESTful API, Postman.

**Mobile**: React Native, React Navigation.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### PERUM PERURI (Sept 2023 - present)

#### HR Management System Planning and Development Section (Contract)

Passed Rekrutmen Bersama BUMN 2023.

- Assisted in developing and managing changes in organizational structure and derivative products and integrating their data into SAP.
- Become a Project Manager and System Designer for the Strategic Human Resources Department's Annual Innovation Projects (ongoing project: Assessment Information System)

# RESEARCH ASSISTANT (Early 2018 - present)

- Assisting lecturer with their research and occasionally helping researchers from abroad that are coming to Bali and needs help researching Balinese Culture.
- In charge of research conferences held by the Faculty of Cultural Sciences at Udayana University.
- I made all event designs, from pamphlets and certificates to book covers.

#### INTERNATIONAL GLOBAL NETWORK (Apr - Dec 2018)

#### Campus Ambassador

- Dealing with enquiries from local press, NGOs, and related organizations, establishing and maintaining the relationship.
- Actively promote IGN events in the local environment and become a committee for MUN events in countries such as Malaysia, and Indonesia.

#### UDAYANA UNIVERSITY, VETERINARY DEPT. (May - Oct 2017)

#### IT Staff Internship

- Cooperated with other interns to create a veterinary master's student registration system using PHP and HTML that integrated with the faculty's website.
- Responsible as a liaison between administrative staff and students, performing various data entries for student needs into the system.

# RECENT EXPERIENCES IN ORGANIZATION AND EVENT

- Bali Asia International Model United Nations 2019. BAIMUN (Volunteer)
- Youth Excursion 2017 in Seoul, South Korea. YOUTEX (Selected Participant)
- 2nd Global Young Leaders Peace Camp in Sri Lanka 2017. GYLPC (Selected Participant)
- 32nd ICSU General Assembly in Bali 2017 (Liaison Officer)